Guide to the Center for American Music Photos CAM.PHOTOS.2017
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Monument in the Rowan Graveyard, Federal Hill, Bardstown, KY (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12624.07)
- Foster bust at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans at CUNY in the Bronx (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12625)
  - Foster statue in the Hall of Fame for Great Americans (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12625.01)
  - Bust of Stephen Foster at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans, CUNY (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12625.02)
  - Stephen Foster and other statues at the Hall of Fame for Great Americans at Cuny in the Bronx (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12625.03)
- Guiseppe Morretti statue of Stephen Foster in Highland Park (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12627)
- Guiseppe Morretti statue of Stephen Foster in Highland Park (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12628)
- Foster statue by Arthur Ivone (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Folder 12629)
  - Foster statue by Arthur Ivone (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12629.01)
  - Foster statue by Arthur Ivone (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12629.02)
- Foster painting, artist unknown (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12630)
- Foster bust by Walter Hancock, Niehaus Model, November 1951 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12631)
- Foster bust by Walter Hancock, Niehaus Model, November 1951 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12632)
- Foster bust by Walter Hancock, Niehaus Model, January, 1952 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12633)
- Foster bust by Walter Hancock, Niehaus Model, January, 1952 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12634)
- Foster bust by Walter Hancock, Niehaus Model, November, 1951 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12635)
- Foster bust by Walter Hancock, Niehaus Model, January, 1952 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12636)
- Stephen Foster Memorial bust presented to the Library of Congress by Mr. Stephen Wigmore, January 12, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12637)
- Marble bust of Stephen Collins Foster made for the Library of Congress by Walker Hancock, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12638)
- Stephen Foster Memorial bust presented to the Library of Congress, January 12, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12639)
- Stephen Foster Memorial bust presented to the Library of Congress, January 12, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12640)
- Stephen Foster Memorial bust presented to the Library of Congress, January 12, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12641)
- Stephen Foster Memorial bust presented to the Library of Congress, January 12, 1953 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12642)
- Stephen Foster's melodeon, photographed at Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12792)
- Eliza Clayland Foster's sampler (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12793)
- Exterior of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12838)
- Exterior of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12839)
- Exterior of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 2, Photos 12840)
- Exterior of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 12841)
- Exterior of Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 12842)
- Cover of London Musical Bouquet edition of "The Old Folks at Home" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13045)
- Cover of "Old Folks at Home" Georgia Southern & Florida Railroad edition (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13046)
- Guiseppe Morretti statue of Stephen Foster, photographed at his New York studio (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13047)
- Oval cropped photo of William Foster and Eliza Clayland Tomlinson Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13048)
- Jane Foster as an old woman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13049)
- Drawing of Tioga Point (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13050)
- Drawing of Athens, PA (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13051)
- Cover of Waters' Golden Harp for Sunday Schools (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13052)
- Pencil sketch of Morrison Foster by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13053)
- Judge John Rowan (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13054)
- Marion Foster as a young girl (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13055)
- Side view of the Foster bust by Arthur Ivone (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13056)
- Portion of the sheet music cover for "Melodies of the New Orleans Serenaders" showing Nelson Kneass (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13057)
- Pencil sketch of Federal Hill in Bardstown, KY (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13058)
- Drawing of the Foster Memorial Home (3600 Penn Avenue) by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13059)
- Pencil sketch of Foster by J. Muller from "daguerreotype pose" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13060)
- Pencil sketch of W. A. Pond by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13061)
- Pencil sketch of W. Roark by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13062)
- Pencil sketch of E. P. Christy by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13063)
- Pencil sketch of George Cooper by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13064)
- Pencil sketch of Judge John Rowan by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13065)
- Pencil sketch of John Rowan, Jr., by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13066)
- Pencil sketch of Horace Waters by J. Muller (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13067)
- Plan of the Town of Lawrenceville laid out by William Foster, September 27, 1847 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13075)
- Box set of Foster Hall Reproductions (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13082)
- Box set of the Foster Hall Reproductions (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13083)
- Box set of Foster Hall Reproductions (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13084)
- Oval photograph of three women identified as Harriet Buchanan, Lidie Wick, and Lottie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13164)
- Close up of three women identified as Harriet Buchanan, Lidie Wick, and Lottie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13165)
- Close up of three women identified as Harriet Buchanan, Lidie Wick, and Lottie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13166)
- Portrait of three women identified as Harriet Buchanan, Lidie Wick, and Lottie Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13214)
- Henrietta Foster Thornton (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13222)
- Unidentified woman (originally misidentified as Mary Wick) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13223)
- Major George H. Crosman (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13224)
- Profile view of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13481)
- Profile view of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13482)
- Profile view of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13483)
- Profile view of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13484)
- Profile view of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13485)
- Profile view of Josiah K. Lilly (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13486)
- Exterior view of snow-covered Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13665)
- Exterior view of snow-covered Foster Hall (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13666)
- Exterior view of Foster Hall, covered in snow (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13667)
- Exterior view of Foster Hall, covered in snow (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13668)
- Small piece of paper reading "Write sonnet or brief verse tribute to Stephen Foster" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13687)
- Letter from Gilbert Eberhart to Morrison Foster, page 1, Oct. 29, 1900 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13688)
- Page from the showing a pantomime of "Old Folks at Home" in The Foster Hall Bulletin, February, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13689)
- continuation of the pantomime of "Old Folks at Home" in The Foster Hall Bulletin, February, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13690)
- page of three of the pantomime of "Old Folks at Home" in The Foster Hall Bulletin, February, 1935 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13691)
- Binders volumes of Foster's music, one stamped Lidie Wick (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13692)
- Hymnal page showing song "Go, Child, and Beg a Bit of Bread!" with music by S.C. Foster, page 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13694)
- Hymnal page showing song "Go, Child, and Beg a Bit of Bread!" with music by S.C. Foster, page 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13695)
- Title page of Clark's School Visitor. Vol. VI, Nov. 5, May 1862 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13718)
- Page from Clark's School Visitor showing "The Merry, Merry Month of May" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13719)
- Title Page for "International Quickstep" by Theodore Schallehn (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13737)
- Front page of Foster's account book showing his signature (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13810)
- Page from Foster's Account Book showing "Blume, Charlotte" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13811)
- Page from Foster's account book showing the names "Foster, Morrison, Foster, Wm B., Jr., and Firth, Pond & Co." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13812)
- Page from Foster's account book showing the name "Samuel Gray" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13813)
- Page from Foster's Account book showing the name "Mrs. Johnston" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13814)
- Page from Foster's account book showing the name "H. Kleber & Bros." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13815)
- Page from Foster's account book beginning with the name "Wish, John" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13816)
- Page from Foster's account book starting with the name "Mrs. M.A. O'Neill" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13817)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled with "Morrison Foster Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13818)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "1. Morrison Foster Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13819)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "3. Wm. B. Foster Jr. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13820)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "3. Wm B. Foster Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13821)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "5. Mrs. M.A. O'Neill Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13822)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "5. Mrs. M.A. O'Neill Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13823)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "7. Firth, Pond & Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13824)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "7. Firth, Pond & Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13825)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "8. Firth, Pond & Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13826)
- Page from Foster's Account Book labeled "8. Firth, Pond, & Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13827)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "9. Firth Pond & Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13828)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "9. Firth Pond & Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13829)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "10. Firth, Pond & Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13830)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "10. Firth, Pond, & Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13831)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "Firth, Pond & Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13832)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "Firth, Pond, & Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13833)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "12 Firth, Pond & Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13834)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "12. Firth, Pond & Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13835)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "29. Pittsburgh Trust Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13836)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "29. Pittsburgh Trust Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13837)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "30. Pittsburgh Trust Co. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13838)
- Page from Foster's account book "30. Pittsburgh Trust Co. Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13839)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "31. John Mish Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13840)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "31. John Mish Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13841)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "32. John Mish Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13842)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "32. John Mish Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13843)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "33. J.M. Little Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13844)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "33. J.M. Little Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13845)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "34. Charlotte Blume Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13846)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "34. Charlotte Blume Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13487)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "35. Samuel Gray Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13848)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "35. Samuel Gray Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13849)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "36. H. Kleber & Bro. Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13850)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "36. H. Kleber Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13851)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "37. Mrs. Johnston Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13852)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "37. Mrs. Johnston Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13853)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "38. Wm. & Jas. Murdock Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13854)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "38. Wm. & Jas. Murdock Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13855)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "39. Wm. H. McCarthy Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13856)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "39. Wm. H. McCarthy Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13857)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "40. A. Miller Dr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13858)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "40. Mrs. A. Miller Cr." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13859)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "Receipts on Music -- Continued" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13861)
- Page from Foster's Account Book labeled "43. Receipts on Music Continued" (crossed out) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13863)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "44. Accounts from Firth, Pond & Co." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13864)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "45. Accounts from Firth, Pond & Co." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13865)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "46. Accounts from Firth, Pond & Co." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13866)
- Page from Foster's account book labeled "47. Total a c/o to July 1/[?] from F.B. & Co." (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 13867)
- Marie Goth portrait of Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14170)
- Image (uncorrected) of a young boy misidentified as Stephen Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14202)
- Reprint of daguerreotype of Eliza Clayland Tomlinson Foster and William Barclay Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14203)
- John N. Carey, Young E. Allison, and Mgr. F.H. Gavisk (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14217)
- Percy F. Smith, publisher of Morrison Foster's (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14218)
- Mrs. Paul, William and Eliza's landlady at the home they boarded at in 1840 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14219)
- Frontispiece image of Eliza and William B. Foster used for "The Old Folks at Home" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14302)
- Reprint (corrected) of image misidentified as Stephen Foster as a young boy (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14303)
- Scrap of paper labeled "Sep 18, 1860" with six songs listed and totals, September 18, 1860 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14320)
- Jane Porter McDowell, Foster's mother-in-law (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14337.01)
- William Walter Welsh, Marion Foster's husband (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14338)
- Jessie Lightner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14339)
- Brothers and sisters: Ann Eliza, Henrietta, Henry, and Morrison Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14340.01)
- Photo of the original fold out frame containing 14340.01 and a photo of Stephen Collins Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14340.02)
- Drawing of the carte de visite of Ann Eliza, Henrietta, Henry and Morrison, 1865 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14340)
- Flypage and title page of Petit Paroissen labeled "Stephen C. Foster's Christmas Gift to Himself", Dec. 25, 1856 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14341)
- Carte de visite of Stephen Foster with a dedication on the back to Jessie Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14342)
- Carte de visite of Marion Foster as a young girl (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14343.01)
- Side by side images of Marion Foster as a young girl (including 14343.01) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14343.02)
- Carte de visite of Marion Foster as a young girl (one of the images included in 14343.02) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14343.03)
- Close up of Marion Foster's face extracted from 14343.01 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14343.04)
- Side by side carte de visite's of Morrison Foster and Henry Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14344)
- Carte de visite of Morrison Foster (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14344.01)
- Side by side carte de visites of Jessie Lightner (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14345)
- Carte de visite of Stephen Foster, signed by him (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14346)
- Letter from Esten Cooke to Stephen Foster, July 26, 1859 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14347)
- Letter from Henry Foster to his sister describing Stephen's death, p. 1, February 4, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14348)
- Letter from Henry Foster to his sister describing Stephen's death, p. 2, February 4, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14349)
- Letter from Henry Foster to his sister describing Stephen's death, p. 3, February 4, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14350)
- Letter from Henry Foster to his sister describing Stephen's death, p. 4, February 4, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14351)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to Ann Eliza, September 15, 1845 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14352)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to Ann Eliza, July 16, 1850 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14353)
- Letter from Henry Foster to Susan Beach, p. 1, January 23, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14354)
- Letter from Henry Foster to Susan Beach, p. 2, January 23, 1864 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14355)
- Letter from Agnes MacDowell to her sister, Mrs. John D. Scully, describing Stephen and Jane's wedding, p. 1 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14356)
- Letter from Agnes MacDowell to her sister, Mrs. John D. Scully, describing Stephen and Jane's wedding, p. 2 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14357)
- Letter from Agnes MacDowell to her sister, Mrs. John D. Scully, describing Stephen and Jane's wedding, p. 3 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14358)
- Letter from Henrietta Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., p. 1, April 30, 1826 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14359)
- Letter from Henrietta Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., p. 2, April 30, 1826 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14360)
- Exterior of letter from Henrietta Foster to William B. Foster, Jr., April 30, 1826 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14361)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 1, November 15, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14567)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 1, p. 2, November 15, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14568)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 3, November 15, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14569)
- Exterior of letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, Nov. 17, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14570)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 1, December 15, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14571)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 2, December 15, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14572)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 1, October 26, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14573)
- Letter from James Buchanan to Reverend Edward Y. Buchanan, p. 2, October 26, 1854 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14574)
- Exterior of Foster Hall in the snow (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14610)
- Flyer advertising (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14622)
- Map showing Lawrenceville and Wainwright Island (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14938)
- Plan of Pittsburgh from "The Travels of H.H. Bernard", 1825-1826 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14939)
- Scrap of paper reading "In company with brother Henry visited the house I was born in at Lawrenceville", August 9, 1843 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14945)
- Drawing of unidentified man (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 14965)
- Collection of Foster Hall publications including the Foster Hall Bulletin, Morrison Foster's My Brother Stephen, and the Foster Hall Reproductions (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15006)
- Henrietta Foster Thornton with two sons (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15092)
- Drawing of music publisher S.T. Gordon (by J. Muller?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15178)
- Sketch of John Firth (by J. Muller?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15179)
- Lithograph entitled "The Late John Firth of New York" (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15180)
- The White Cottage, original panting by Mr. Miller, 1828 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15185)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to J.B. Russell, p. 1, January 28, 1857 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15553)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to J.B. Russell, p. 2, January 28, 1857 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15554)
- Foster family descendants (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15723.01)
- Foster family descendants (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15723)
- Scully family group picture (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15724)
- Foster family descendants, including Marion Foster Welch, seated in the sitting room of the Foster Memorial Home (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15725)
- John D. Scully, black and white (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15726.01)
- John D. Scully, in color (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15726)
- Stephen Foster Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15790)
- Dallas Clayland Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15791)
- Marshall Foster Reed (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15792)
- Dorothy Jane Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15793)
- Virginia Clarissa Reed (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15794)
- Mrs. Ernest A. Reed (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15795)
- Mrs. Ernest A. Reed with her children, Virgninia Clarissa Reed and Marshall Foster Reed (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15796)
- Mrs. Ernest A. Reed, Virginia Clarissa Reed, and Mrs. Jessie Welsh Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15797)
- Virginia Clarissa Reed (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15798)
- Jessie Rose (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 15882)
- Drawing of W.C. Peters (by J. Muller?) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 16307)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to G.W. Birdseye, Feb. 11, 1863 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 16406)
- Architect's drawing of Stephen Foster Memorial (final accepted) (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 16531)
- Four images on a page that were used to create lantern slides: Foster's wallet and note; Mssrs Firth and Pond; covers for "Ellen Bayne" and "Willie We Have Missed You"; Athens and Tioga Point (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 16807)
- Letter from Stephen Foster to William Hamilton, p. 1, and a letter from William Hamilton authenticating the letter, January 16, 1857 (File-cabinet 15, Drawer 3, Photos 17072)